Look at Riza's creativity.  He took
out my earrings and all that and gave them to me.  Hi friends
Assalam Walekum.  Welcome all of you to the world of Khushamdid Saba.  I
hope
you all are well.  Alhamdulillah, with your blessings,
we are all fine.  I just
need your blessings.  And friends, as
I told you in the last blog,
I have to do a photo shoot, get ready a little and
wear that long necklace.  I
will show you how I get ready.  I do it simply.  That's why
I am wearing such an outfit and
I have borrowed this outfit from Riza.  So that's why
I have worn such an outfit in which that
necklace will be highlighted.  Let its meaning be known.
I have to put on makeup before wearing this friends jewellery.  You will have to wear it again,
otherwise it will look different.
Friends, he saw me getting ready again
and saw all this.  Today it is
asking for too much.  He is crying, please take this out and give it to me.
[Music]
Friends, I had kept hair serum and after that
Ammi asked Krishna what, he said
serum and Ammi applied it and it was for hair,
she applied it, she applied it in her mouth
properly, I cannot tell what it is,
Krishna says, you have applied serum
everywhere [sound of clearing throat] so
poor guy, remove it quickly, it is for hair, then he asked,
you people say that Ammi is very innocent, she has applied it
only, then we thought that she
applies it only in her mouth.  It is of hair.
No, he did not tell me that this has to be
applied on the hair.
Friends, when I was so ready, then I thought that
I should take a photo near the plan so that I
remember when I was
so properly ready.
How are you feeling?
This necklace looks so nice.  Do you know
how much it is blooming?  Even the necklace which is not selling will be
sold.
Inshallah Allah,
I did not feel that anyone would wear a necklace,
but now after seeing it, it looks so good.   Thank
you.  You gave me the outfit.
What?  Outfits are
useful like this only.  Sometimes I took someone's [laughs]
, sometimes someone else's.   Come on, get up
quickly.
I have learned these new and unique things
about every tradition on Instagram and have
told you all about them too.  So it feels good that through this
I also get knowledge and I
also share my knowledge with you.
If there is shortage of cloves then we will take it from this.
Give it to mom.  Mom eats a lot of cloves.   It
is a real clove.   It
is a real clove.  The real key is long.
This silver is also real.   The
silver is real.  Ok.  Well then.  It had rained.  The
cloves will get spoiled.
Why will it need water?   The
bride wears it, right?  Then keep it with you.
Then keep it wrapped.
So look, it looks good.
Feeling good, right?
You liked Riza at Riza's wedding, right?  Is there
a person at your wedding?
Hey, this doesn't happen.  I liked it, so
friends, do you know what I am going to make today
?  Today I am making Chole
Bhature.  Proper Delhi style chole bhature.
Husband Sahib's question: Where has your husband gone?
Where did the husband go [laughter]?  I am not even looking.
So what is
their demand?   Will
you really make Bhature?  are looking.
So right now we are going to buy all these vegetables for him.
So now first of all this gets ready.
Do this and that, it is 15th August.
Yes, Haider on the day of independence, but Baba
Haider did not become free.  Haider, Baba did not become free from Mama.
Hey sir, what's the matter?
And look here also, look here in our society also.
Vegetables can be made.  Take beet root and
that barbati also.  Do you know Barbati
friends?
This is it,
friends, after coming to Mumbai we came to know about this dance.
So before that we knew only about
this,
yes
in UP they
make it like this, stuffing it with masala and wrapping it with a thread, right? It
won't be made by wrapping it with a thread like this,
Bhaiya must have eaten it, Bhaiya must know, so
she makes it without the thread as well,
yes, stuffing it without the thread,
yes now I
look like a rat, you know the
rates here are good, you know, it is
very expensive outside, this one is
stuffing,
buy it, then this one is also stuffing, now
you have become the complete owner,
what do you want to buy, do you
want the small one,
how much does this one cost, the
head is
also small, it is not suitable for carrying, another friend got
so
excited after seeing it that she felt like buying everything,
Lauki will say why did you break me,
friend, all our preparations for 15th August are done,
we have just bought the stuff from here, now
we will go home, will Chole Bhature be made today or
not, hurry up, please
hurry up,
we had gone to buy stuff for our daughter, 15th August is
tomorrow, so
look who has brought this, it is
Haider's, is
n't it, for the
first time something new has come  It was there, I have never seen anything like this before, oh
wow, they did
n't come before, new ones did
n't come, they used to come like this, these have just come,
look what is this, is this a
clip for clipping photos, this one has
also just come, call me, let's go, yes, bring it to me
quickly,
friends, there were so many cute things for the girls there, he wo
n't put anything, so
daughter, we brought all this, we will
decorate the restaurant with this, this one is
for the restaurant and this Rida will decorate herself and she will make it herself, I will make it
completely like this,
yes, you decorate yourself first, I mean, you
brought it for her, but you are doing everything first, I
also feel like it, friends, I did
not understand, you can
take any one of these, all are the same thing,
oh, take it now, you will take it, I know, you will take it, no,
first you have to take the dupatta, the dupatta, the
friends in the restaurant, our waiters, all the
people who will take the orders, they will put it, the
couple that we ordered for Haider, have come, the
size is also okay, right?
Yes, it is very good, the
size is also okay, va nice va nice
Haider was starting to walk, you all are so much  He
is happy Alhamdulillah Mashaallah may Allah
give such health to all the children what is there in it I wanted to
make gulagula but could not make it yet I have to
offer Fatiha also so that my
health gets a little better Inshallah we will do it again in a day
So friends, we are now in the kitchen and we will start
making bhaturas first because
we will make bhaturas first because in the
recipe we have seen it is mentioned that it should be
kept first friends you must have
made it all of you the whole world must have made chole bhature
this flour will be needed semolina will be needed curd
sugar salt no sugar now
sugar will not be needed
one spoon
sugar will be needed in which
one spoon will be needed
in this bhatura
yes
brother where is the sugar to be added if it is to be added we will
tell you in detail we will
put it the
channel people are liars
theirs too but this is the truth
friend tauba tauba tauba tauba no you
[laughs] do not believe the words at all
you do not put sugar this much it is enough there are
many people in our house it is less  Then the
biggest result is something alive that
look at mine, there are 10 people in our house,
four Amma will eat Bhature, six Rihaan will eat
[laughs]
okay, four five these people will eat, four five you will
eat, one I will eat Amma your daughter will eat,
at least seven eight
and half half [laughs] Haider will eat,
half Haider will eat, if it is done then make more.
This is flour.  Add half the amount of semolina.  It will
just be too much.
Pot as much as you want means half of the
recipe will be the last person the world will end.
When someone will eat after seeing Sawa's recipe
[laughs]
I was going to ask you the same thing that
who will cook after seeing your recipe?
You said it yourself.   There must be
someone.  So we
added semolina and salt.  There won't be too much salt.
No, put it in.
How do you add salt like this?  What do you mean?
Leave it for five minutes.
And this has baking soda in it.  Today my
heart is telling me that you will make it, they will turn out
good today, bring some sugar from inside me too, did
n't you say anything before, did she drive her sister away
because she was jealous, she was pushing her ahead, even now while leaving
from there she is saying does the
curd turn out soft, why, when she is
not giving you a lift, then why am I telling you every day, get
ready,
yes just get ready, otherwise it will turn into sweet puri,
you will see if you eat it in such a way that you kiss my hands,
friend, now we will see whether we will kiss his hands
or we will break his hands, now it doesn't matter,
I am motivating you, you will not even give him water to
drink, if not water, then we will
spoil it.  And
friends, we have also added some oil in it.  And now we will add water to it.
how much water?
So friends, now I will knead its dough.
Kneading the dough is the hardest part.  Look friend,
I am the one who does it.  Now when that camera is switched off,
I will have to do it.   Oh my god, I have
spoiled your mood.
Why are you calling me bad?  [laughter]
So bad, we say so ourselves.
Whatever I want to say, my
commenters say it.
I am supporting those who have commented on them.
You are hitting like this.  If I did it like this, it would
stick to the top [laughs].
All your work is done.  He is the straight one.
Hey, now tell me this, is killing meant to be eaten?   Do
n't break the tiles below.  Those people take it and
kill in this.  Quickly, quickly, quickly, I have to
hit him like this for a long time.
He's got to be beaten up a lot until he improves [laughs].   You have
cracked a great joke.
Friends is so messed up.  I do
n't know what kind of goo this is.   Try being
softer now.  Now its turn.   I have to
keep it now.
Yes.
Save Sunil.  It is found.
Friends, we were having a small
meeting here.  So I had to see that too.
Cooking also had to be done simultaneously.  That's why I have
turned off the sound here because some noise was coming.  Let
us start making it.
Some of our friends have kept spices there.
Some of us had this one so it's very
good.  Whole spices have to be added to it.   Done it.
She is saying go and check.
Let's see the wedding very much.  I mean, I have
created so much in my life but I have not
seen so much.  Look at this, because mine has
not puffed up till date, maybe I
rubbed it a lot in the end, I pressed it a
lot and see how much it is
made like this, less will be made in this, that dosa is
not dosa, this is oh that is oh
bhatura, whatever it is,
what is bhatura, this is
aloo bukhara,
mom says aloo bukhara,
I said take the parora, mother, the people of Mauda
like it, I did
not get the patora here also, I
brought it for mom, I did not bring it for myself,
we do not eat the parora,
everyone will eat it, I will give it to you,
I will go to the restaurant right now, as long as
I am here at home, I am watching
their scene.  Now I have covered it with a lid
because the presence of onion is the biggest factor in
how much your masala gets roasted.
See, unless the onions are fried, it will not
be cooked well.
Our tea is ready.  First we drank tea, if
I had made it then I would
not have ground the onion.  know why?  When you
cut onions into thin slices vertically.  She gets it in a good way.
And ground onion for a
very long time.
All expert advice will come.
I said it earlier.
She is also giving it from behind.  What?  No, you
can add potatoes to chicken or anything else,
if you fry it well then it gets completely
mixed.  I should have pointed out the
mistake beforehand. By the time the video is
ready and uploaded on YouTube,
how many mistakes will be found?
Grind it or not, it is a good thing if you grind it otherwise it will get mushy.
So friends,
our tea break has just ended, let's start working after tea. A
few moments later,
friends, we grind it and then add it, but as Sunny
asked me to, I added it like this, so
now you take care of your household responsibilities, I am
going to the restaurant. Okay
friends, I will add all the spices like cumin
powder, dry mango powder, chole masala,
this much is enough.  Friends, now we will add chickpeas in it.
One Hour [Music] Later.
Chole is ready.   The
chole are ready.  Look,
show me.
Wow, you look good.  Made in marriage.   Just like the
Nagamani is
kept safe and preserved.  We have saved it completely like this.
Mom's son.
So friends, everything is done now, then something or the other will go
wrong, the oil should crackle
very quickly, it should crackle tomorrow, do
n't teach now,
your teacher is standing here, don't teach now,
everything is going so well,
look how well it is going,
my dear sister,
my dear son, look, there is no dear husband,
Bismillah Rahman Rahim, he has
weakened it a bit,
Sunny Bhai, add oil quickly,
where will the
spoon come from [laughs]
Amma has become professional, how is your chole
bhature looking, look
this was also in the smiling recipe, friends, but there is a
little more oil, less chilli
[laughs]
why did he say
poor thing, how is this, we are also scared, you know she has
climbed behind, he added it and said,
after cooking, friends, we went to meet
our Api Reshma Api for 10 minutes,
we had
coffee there and we came home, till now
how many chole we have made, they look
good, they are mixed well,
not much, we
made a bowl and bhaturas, they were
good, they were home made,
yes
Show me that,
see this, it is well done,
yes mom, friends, I have come only in the night,
mom was a little busy today, tomorrow is 15th August.  Happy
Independence Day [laughs] May
Allah bless everyone.  That's all there is to it.
Just let Sunny like it.  That's it
because he said with such heart that
you don't make anything good.  Non-veg
is mostly available now.  You
know we have a restaurant.  It is so
good there that we buy it from there and
then sometimes green vegetables should also be eaten at home, not just sometimes, but at least at
one time.  So
then Sunny
just checks it and tells me
how it is made.  These bhaturas look good.
Give it to him completely.   They have become
absolutely perfect.  Okay,
bring my name,
yes, it is
such a big name [crying sound] she
cooks everything, sometimes if she doesn't feel like cooking, she
says she doesn't know how to cook, but she
can cook biryani, khichdi, chicken, she cooks everything, they are
very good
and after Sunny, if someone likes chole
and I am his
brother, I am at second place [laughs] first place,
Risha liked it very much
because I don't eat non-veg much, I like
only veg, daughter,
how did you like the song?   I liked it.   If
everyone likes it then it gives me great happiness.
Now I get more motivation when everyone praises
me to try more things in the future.
Friends have now also become content creators.
So there is college tomorrow but what is this nervousness of mine,
it is not going well because of this.
I also want to make it, so I am going and getting myself
ready.  As long as she does this.
Mom is your favorite thing.
Sunny took this.  Mom, especially for you.
I did not take this.  He knows Amma,
Mauda's Amma likes Paroora, I had told her once,
I was looking for it for a long time, I will make it
and then feed it to you, okay,
Amma will eat this much, I
brought it from there,
Amma, how would I know, she just brought
half,
then I will bring more,
Amma, I will make it tomorrow, everything is completely homemade, this much is
not nectar, it is
more than nectar, all are wild fruits, there is no
adulteration in it, nothing, it grows
in the bush and comes once in a year, one should
definitely eat it once or twice.
Show me where is the white?   It
is not white.  There are white eyes [laughs].   Should
I forget one thing?  Your makeup looks really bad.  The
orange one.
Oh, it happened with great difficulty.  Then half the
reel would go waste.
Hot momma has applied it herself.  So will I also
wear white tomorrow?
[Music]
Friends, on behalf of the three of us, we wish you all a
very happy Independence Day.  So today is a day of happiness, so
we are also celebrating and
our child is also celebrating with us.
So friends, we came here to
take photos and videos.  So it's done now
how straight it is made.
Later that same evening.  So come on guys let's
start the preparation now.  Every
time, like on 26th January or 15th August, we
always make something special.
Make it.  I am not feeling well at all today.
Today Dhihaan will do all the work.  I will keep
telling you and keep doing it.  Ok.   First of all,
install the cylinder there.   Haven't installed it yet.
But where is the cylinder?  [laughter]
Well, how do I turn it off?
Hey Rihaan, don't do anything else.   There is a
smell of gas.   Don't do it, don't do it.
Rihaan let it be.
How did you like it?
I made this yesterday.  Is good.
Ok.
You seem okay.
[laughter]
Oh ma'am, who puts it in the milk?   Turn on the
gas first.
How does milk curdle?  Add vinegar.   I have
also seen the recipe.  You just picked it up and came here.   You should
watch it once, apart from that you should
watch it.  We are making something.
Everyone will eat it.
Hey when I'm a no fight no fight.
This country became independent only because of your fight.
[laughs]
Let the syrup prepare first, otherwise it will take time.   That's it, that's it,
Rihaan is not complete.  Look Rihaan, this is
right.
Look friends, Rihaan had said that he will make it
today.  He is
asking me everything.  What is the point of me making it?   If you look back
a little, she had said
that she would guide you completely.
I will keep telling you and keep doing it.  Ok.
Shalu had said in the beginning that I will
make it.  I have to take them out today
because when there is such a special occasion,
these people also have expectations
and I also feel like let's show them
our lighting decoration for 15th August,
so these people said that we will
make something, I had gone to meet Bhabhi,
I have come back after an hour, I thought everything would be ready
and when I came, it was still there.
Is this Rasgulla or Chhena?   Is it
chenna or rasgulla?
Both say
both.
Let's do that to him.  Filter it by putting it in a sieve.
We bought 2 litres of milk and left with only that much.
That's why they are expensive.   I am
making something like this for the first time.  Yes,
last time I made Kheer Puri.  Remember
?   I
saw how many kheer puris Rihaan had made.   If you want to
eat, just ask.
Who is saying anything?  I am saying that
you made it, right?  You have to take the hand like this and
rub it like this.  They spoil the whole dough like this.  You have to
knead the dough for kheer puri.
Hey, it will be fun.   It is
dirty anyway.  If you partition it separately then it is
not there.
[laughter]
We'll have to call our chef now.  Now
tell me what has happened now?
Our round round is not happening.   The
thing is, it sticks.
Who has seen it anyway?  I also saw it.
He said [laughter] that he had seen it.   It is done.
Look, my hands are
with me.  Ok.  Make it like this because
his mother is with me.
Look at the syrup and tell me whether Shalu's is good or
not?   It is a
little thicker.  It will definitely be thick.
I'm a little thin without it, right?  Do
n't make so much syrup, keep it ready.  [laughter]
Add more sugar.  Keep the syrup filled completely.
Peace, its syrup, a little water,
friends, this is the same example that the village was
not settled, robbers came first, sweet was not made,
gluttons came first,
add some more sugar, it is very thin, Reeza,
eat it quickly, it will be ready,
tell me, won't you [laughs] I ca
n't believe it
when death comes, don't we eat it,
tell me, wow, what is there in this, I like it so much, it does
n't harm people,
why, what is it, it is whole milk, it has
sugar, it won't harm them, they are
better than gulab jamun,
tell me, you are making everything, you did not add any color,
tell me, does anyone remember this recipe Rihaan, oh, but it was
not told in the recipe
that we should make the tricolor, do
one thing, if you want to
make a tricolor, then use this white one,
make the orange one separately,
yes, you do one thing, we will leave four-five of them, the
rest for this,
yes,
you did not give the idea
Rihaan, I was about to make it, oh
you are sleeping, oh shut up about me, so
what was I saying to you,
an idea came to my mind, like in Farah Ma'am's show,
Farah Ma'am goes to everyone's house.  So I am thinking
I should invite everyone to my house.
Oh wow, that's good.
What kind of idea is this?  Subscribers can also be called.
What kind of idea is this?  Your kitchen is ready.
Like today Rihaan is making his
recipe.  Sometimes someone can make it their own.
But subscribers have come here with their recipes.
Yes, that's my [laughs], I have to
show them my specialty
here.
One two three Bismillah.
This is how it happens, right?
I won't eat even one.  Wow, he
looks good Rihaan.  This is very well
done friends.
Hey, to be honest, when the camera was off.  Hey, tell me the truth.
No, no, this is wrong or incorrect.
I said softly that this upper one should
put something like this in it.  The speed is very good.
Yes.
If you do it like this, you can cut it and eat it.   That's
correct.
According to the jar, it is getting dry.  So
if we take it out like this, it will fall.   There
is dry colored chenna here.
What?   You have
brought such a big green one.  The one I
eat is the smaller one.  You have brought such a small one.   There
is no flower.  There is a big flower, so I have brought it.
No, let me
eat the flower first, then
why are you not giving me the bigger one?  No,
eat the big one, eat it, it's a lot, isn't it, the big one,
really, I haven't seen it,
you will eat it all, eat it, eat it, eat it,
tell me how is it, did
you eat it [laughs]
tell me,
first, your chenna,
not mine, Rihaan made it, Rihaan,
then let me see this one,
I had already told you,
Rihaan brought it, so listen to the praises of your chenna,
mom tried yours, I have
n't tried it yet, she liked it so much, she liked it so much, seriously,
really,
yes, I haven't eaten it yet, a
little bit, I want
diet
flavor, nothing,
we are also not on diet [laughs] I will eat it,
okay, have
I made some poison on my hands,
yes, it's not
raw [laughs] I was
saying raw, I've
seen it,
but you haven't said all this before,
but what do I care,
friends, it's not that bad, don't fight,
it's good, the sugar hasn't
reached inside it, just take it and good, nice try, so
friends, as you know that today is
Independence Day, so we all thought of
making such packets by putting all the chips, fruity and biscuits in it and
we will give it to whoever we find there.  Tell me
friends, we had just left and Sunny could
not go because there was a
lot of work in Mashallah restaurant and after that let us
show you where the decoration has been done in Mumbai.  It
looked very beautiful
wherever there was decoration.  Friends, the
best lighting and
decoration in Mumbai is that of the
CST station here.  So look at this,
very cute, very
[music]
we